<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="66">
  <author>yumi</author>
  <version>0.0.0.2</version>
  <contributors>yumi, mrbear, jujuokl, alpha117,FomaDNS</contributors>
  <title>
    <en>ContractorMod</en>
  </title>
  <description>
    <en><![CDATA[
This mod enable simulating a defined number of characters you control one by one during a solo game.

By default, 4 characters are available Alex, Brenda, Chris and David.
At first loading of a map, they are located at the Career starting point.
When saving the game, characters location and vehicle is saved so they will be restored when next loading the game.
So you will be able to continue your game exactly as you left it.

Default keys to switch between characters are:
- NEXT    : Tab
- PREVIOUS: Shift + Tab
They can be changed but by default they replaced the standard switch between vehicles since it's disable.

This mod is compatible with CoursePlay and FollowMe mods.
So, for example, when using FollowMe, one character will be the Leader and another one the Follower.
Characters can be seen on the minimap when activating default category (the last one represented by a house) in the map overview screen.

Name, gender, color, body, hair, accessories and number of characters can be changed in ContractorMod.xml file located in modsSettings directory for new games.
Once a game has been saved, they can be changed in ContractorMod.xml file present in related savegame folder.
ContractorMod.xml file also contains configuration for passengers for mods vehicles. You can add your own mods here.
]]></en>
    <de><![CDATA[
Dieser Mod ermöglicht das Simulieren einer definierten Anzahl von Charakteren, die Du während eines Einzelspieler-Spiels einzeln kontrollierst.

Standardmäßig sind 4 Charaktere verfügbar: Alex, Brenda, Chris und David.
Beim erstmaligen Laden einer Karte befinden sie sich am Karrierestartpunkt.
Beim Speichern des Spiels werden der Standort des Charakters und des Fahrzeugs gespeichert, damit diese beim nächsten Laden des Spiels wiederhergestellt werden.
So können Sie Ihr Spiel genauso fortsetzen, wie Sie es verlassen haben.

Standard Tastenbelegung zum Wechseln zwischen Charakteren ist:
- NÄCHSTER: Tab
- VORHERIGER: Umschalt + Tab
Die Belegung kann geändert werden, aber standardmäßig ersetzen sie den Switch zwischen Fahrzeugen, da diese Funktion deaktiviert ist.

Dieser Mod ist kompatibel mit CoursePlay und FollowMe.
So wird zum Beispiel bei der Verwendung von FollowMe ein Charakter der Leader und ein weiterer der Follower sein.
Charaktere können auf der Minikarte gesehen werden, wenn die Standardkategorie (die letzte durch ein Haus repräsentiert) im Kartenübersichtsbildschirm aktiviert wird.

Name, Geschlecht, Farbe, Körper, Haar, Accessoires und Anzahl der Zeichen können in der ContractorMod.xml Datei im Ordner modsSettings für neue Spiele geändert werden.
Sobald ein Spiel gespeichert wurde, kann es in der Datei ContractorMod.xml geändert werden, die im zugehörigen Spielstandsordner vorhanden ist.
ContractorMod.xml enthält auch die Konfiguration von Passagieren für Mod-Fahrzeuge. Sie können hier Ihre eigenen Mods hinzufügen.
]]></de>
    <fr><![CDATA[
Ce mod permet de simuler un nombre défini de personnages différents durant une partie solo que vous controlez tour à tour.

Par défaut, 4 personnages sont disponibles Alex, Brenda, Chris et David.
Au premier chargement d'une map ils sont positionnés au point de départ de la map.
Dès la première sauvegarde, les positions/véhicules des perso sont sauvegardés et seront rechargés au prochain chargement.
Vous pouvez ainsi reprendre la partie exactement là où vous l'avez laissé.

Les touches par défaut pour passer d'un perso à l'autre sont:
- SUIVANT   : Tab
- PRECEDENT : Shift + Tab
Ces touches peuvent être personnalisées et remplacent le switch standard de véhicules qui est désactivé dans le mod.

Ce mod est compatible avec les mods CoursePlay et FollowMe.
Ainsi, en mode FollowMe par exemple, un perso sera le Leader et un autre perso le Follower.
Les perso sont visibles sur la minimap lorsque la catégorie par défaut (la dernière représentée par une maison) est activée dans la vue Aperçu de la carte.

Le nom, le genre, la couleur, le corps, les cheveux, les accessoires et le nombre de perso peuvent être modifiés dans le fichier ContractorMod.xml situé dans le dossier modsSettings pour les nouvelles parties.
Une fois la partie sauvegardée, les modifications se font dans le fichier ContractorMod.xml du répertoire de sauvegarde habituel (savegame..).
Le fichier ContractorMod.xml contient aussi la configuration des passagers pour les véhicules mods. Vous pouvez ajoutez vos propres mods ici.
]]></fr>
    <br><![CDATA[
Este mod permite simular um número definido de personagens que você controla um por um durante um jogo solo.

Por padrão, 4 personagens estão disponíveis: Alex, Brenda, Chris e David.
No primeiro carregamento de um mapa, eles estão localizados no ponto inicial da carreira.
Ao salvar o jogo, a localização dos personagens e o veículo são salvos, então eles serão restaurados no próximo carregamento do jogo.
Então você poderá continuar seu jogo exatamente como você o deixou.

As teclas padrão para alternar entre os personagens são:
- PRÓXIMO  : Tab
- ANTERIOR : Shift + Tab
Eles podem ser alterados, mas, por padrão, eles substituíram o interruptor padrão entre veículos, já que ele é desativado.

Este mod é compatível com os mods CoursePlay e FollowMe.
Assim, por exemplo, ao usar o FollowMe, um personagem será o Líder e outro o Seguidor.
Os personagens podem ser vistos no minimapa ao ativar a categoria padrão (a última representada por uma casa) na tela de visão geral do mapa.

Nome, sexo, cor, corpo, cabelo, acessórios e número de personagens podem ser alterados no arquivo ContractorMod.xml para novos jogos.
Uma vez que um jogo tenha sido salvo, ele pode ser alterado no arquivo ContractorMod.xml, presente na pasta relacionada do savegame.
O arquivo ContractorMod.xml também contém configuração para passageiros para mods de veículos. Você pode adicionar seus próprios mods aqui.
]]></br>
  </description>
  <iconFilename>images/icon_ContractorMod.dds</iconFilename>

  <l10n filenamePrefix="modDesc_l10n" /> <!-- Load the corresponding modDesc_l10n_<language>.XML file, or revert to 'en'/'de'. -->

  <extraSourceFiles>
    <sourceFile filename="scripts/ContractorMod.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="scripts/ContractorModWorker.lua" />
  </extraSourceFiles>
  
  <actions>
    <action name="ContractorMod_WORKER1" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE"/>
    <action name="ContractorMod_WORKER2" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE"/>
    <action name="ContractorMod_WORKER3" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE"/>
    <action name="ContractorMod_WORKER4" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE"/>
    <action name="ContractorMod_WORKER5" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE"/>
    <action name="ContractorMod_WORKER6" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE"/>
    <action name="ContractorMod_WORKER7" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE"/>
    <action name="ContractorMod_WORKER8" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE"/>
  </actions>
  <inputBinding>
    <actionBinding action="ContractorMod_WORKER1">
        <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_1" axisComponent="+" inputComponent="+" index="1"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="ContractorMod_WORKER2">
        <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_2" axisComponent="+" inputComponent="+" index="1"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="ContractorMod_WORKER3">
        <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_3" axisComponent="+" inputComponent="+" index="1"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="ContractorMod_WORKER4">
        <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_4" axisComponent="+" inputComponent="+" index="1"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="ContractorMod_WORKER5">
        <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_5" axisComponent="+" inputComponent="+" index="1"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="ContractorMod_WORKER6">
        <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_6" axisComponent="+" inputComponent="+" index="1"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="ContractorMod_WORKER7">
        <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_7" axisComponent="+" inputComponent="+" index="1"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="ContractorMod_WORKER8">
        <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_8" axisComponent="+" inputComponent="+" index="1"/>
    </actionBinding>
  </inputBinding>

</modDesc>
    
